Gabriel Manfroi

Web Developer

Well-qualified Full Stack Developer familiar with wide range of programming utilities and languages. Knowledgeable of backend and frontend development requirements. Handles any part of process with ease. Collaborative team player with excellent technical abilities offering 5 years of related experience.

Work History

2021-04 -Current

Full Stack Web Developer

TBDC Agro Softwares, Nova Mutum (Remote), Mato Grosso

- Used React, Vue, MongoDB, MySQL, Node and Typescript to develop app-solutions.
- Designed and developed efficient and maintainable software according to business objectives and needs of various clients.
- Reviewed code, debugged problems and corrected issues.
- Adjusted design parameters to boost performance and incorporate new features.
- Orchestrated efficient large-scale software deployments, including testing features and correcting code.
- Reviewed code to validate structures, assess security and verify browser, device and operating system compatibility.

2021-02 -2021-04

Full Stack Developer

Viasoft, Pato Branco, Paraná

- Reviewed code, debugged problems and corrected issues.
- Contributed ideas and suggestions in team meetings and delivered updates on deadlines, designs and enhancements.

•

Employed coding practices based on commonly

Contact

Address

Pato Branco, PR, 85503355

Phone

469921107962

E-mail

manfroigab@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com /in/gabriel-manfroi/

Skills

Application development



Web development projects



Programming



Excellent work ethic



Leadership



Software

JavaScript



accepted standards to establish site layout and user interface.

- Planned and engineered RESTful web services to manipulate dynamic datasets.
- Wrote production-ready code with fluency in modern front-end and back-end frameworks.
- Built front-end web Interface for engineers to control and monitor onboard system that visualized perceived surroundings and set routes of autonomous driving system.

2020-10 - Java Full Stack Developer

2021-02

2019-03

Supera Sistemas, Pato Branco, Paraná

- Participated in complete software development lifecycle, including performance analysis, design, development and testing.
- Participated in requirements gathering and design development meetings.
- Reviewed code and debugged errors to improve performance.
- Developed robust Java code for Web applications.
- Researched new technologies, software packages and hardware products for use in website projects.
- Wrote, modified and maintained software documentation and specifications.

2017-11 - Production Leader

HEXBits Tecnologia, Curitiba, Paraná

- Monitored workers on site during production activities for safety procedures compliance.
- Worked with supervisor and other team leads to manage and prioritize staffing assignments to meet customer demand and production schedules.
- Updated production metrics and facilitate regular team communication.
- Kept records of equipment, budgets, deliveries and supplies and made paperwork available to management for evaluation.
- Made sure that products were produced on time and are of good quality.
- Inspected finished products for quality and adherence to customer specifications.

React

Excellent

●●●● Excellent

Python

Excellent

Flutter

Very Good

Node

Very Good

MySQL

Excellent

MongoDB

Good

REST API's

••••• Excellent

Languages

English

Excellent

Portuguese

••••• Excellent

French

• • • • • • Average

- Oversaw logistics and inventory management for storeroom.
- Prepared reports and technical documentation of day-to-day production processes.

2014-04 -2017-11

IT Assistant

Proserv & Solution Informática, Pato Branco, Paraná

- Installed and configured software and hardware.
- Reviewed system and network performance to make proactive adjustments based on established IT policies.
- Maintained current software licenses and patched applications to stay up-to-date with latest features.
- Configured hardware, devices and software to set up work stations for employees.
- Followed up with clients to verify optimal customer satisfaction following support engagement and problem resolution.
- Removed malware, ransomware and other threats from laptops and desktop systems.

Education

2020-07 -Current

Associate of Technology: Systems Analysis And Development

UNIDEP - Pato Branco

2018-07 -2020-06 **Associate of Mechatronics: Mechatronics**

Pontifícia Universidade Católica Do Paraná - Curitiba

2014-03 -2018-06

Bachelor's: Computer Engineering

Pontifícia Universidade Católica Do Paraná - Curitiba Interrupted in the 9th semester

Projects

BM Engenharia Institutional Website

Institutional Website Developed With Django, PosgreSQL, HTML, CSS and JavaScript https://bmengenharia.eng.br/ 2020 - 2020

COM Serial Reader

Serial Port Reader developed with Python, it starts to communicate with the selected port and prints on the screen the read value

https://github.com/gabemanfroi/PythonSerialReader 2021 - 2021

Proserv & Solution Institutional Website

Instituional Website Developed with Python, Django, PostgreSQL, CSS, HTML and JavaScript https://proservpb.com.br/2020 - 2020

Movelt App

App developed with ReactJS, the goal of the project was to create a challenge app that reminds the user to make some labor gymnastics

https://moveit-gabemanfroi.vercel.app/ 2021 - 2021

Star Wars Crew APP

Project developed in ReactJS, consuming the Star Wars API. The goal was to fetch some data from the api as the character names, planets they visited and create their avatar with the "avataaars" react framework https://github.com/gabemanfroi/star-wars-crew 2021 - 2021